prosperityhotline.com 2009-01-29

# ProsperityHotline.com | Privacy Policy

* * *

**Prosperity Hotline**

Yvonne Anderson's

**ProsperityHotline.com** has created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.

This site contains links to third-party sites.  **ProsperityHotline.com** is NOT responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Why did you receive an email from us?**   
If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.   
  
**How we protect your privacy** ****  
We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.  We employ the services of 1ShoppingCart for delivery of the PH newsletter and the PH Report.  1ShoppingCart and **ProsperityHotline.com** agree not to sell or rent the email addresses of any list member to any third-party.  
**  
****Sharing and Usage**   
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information.  
  
**How can you stop receiving email from us?**   
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email. **Changes to this statement**   
**ProsperityHotline.com** has the discretion to  occasionally revise this privacy statement.  When we do, we will all revise the "updated" date at the top of this page.  We encourage you to periodically review this statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information that we collect.  Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy policy and any updated.

**ProsperityHotline.com Privacy Policy  
******This document was last updated on September 23, 2006.  

_Legitimate Ways for the AVERAGE person to ** _FINALLY_ **Make Money From Home!  
_

**[Home](http://www.prosperityhotline.com/) | [About Yvonne](http://www.prosperityhotline.com/about-yvonne-anderson.html) |  [Articles](http://www.prosperityhotline.com/articles.html) | [Privacy](http://www.prosperityhotline.com/privacy-policy.html) | [Contact](http://www.prosperityhotline.com/contact-yvonne.html) | [Links](http://www.prosperityhotline.com/links/)** **Copyright © 2006 - 2008 ProsperityHotline.com  
All Rights Reserved Worldwide.  
Reproduction in whole or in part without express written permission is prohibited.  Violators will be prosecuted.

Yvonne Anderson's Prosperity Hotline   
Legitimate Ways for the Average Person to _FINALLY_ Make Money From Home

Powered by

**   
****
